That India's first mission which
gives you reimbursement of your medical expenses every month without
hospitalization.
Here you can get rid of these medical expenses in 3
steps. Download the app, sign up for membership,
upload your medical bill,
you will be reimbursed your medical expenses every month without hospitalization
and contact Paaji and get
ICSE long medical insurance up to Rs. 1 lakh.
Medical insurance covers your hospital
expenses but it does not cover the expenses you incur every month
on your medicines and diseases.
Medical
reimbursement membership
covers those monthly expenses which are
not covered in medical insurance, whether it is
related to diabetes or
for doctor's visiting charges due to age
or for putting a bandage on your child's injury.
Today we are going to reimburse you all your expenses, from small to big,
without hospitalization.
We give you an opportunity that instead of spending on medicines and
diseases, you can spend that money on the happiness of your family.
Our basic plan is Rs.
45000 plus tasty, on that
you get medical bills.
Validity of reimbursement frees Now
Scan Addison has
this mantra Reimbursement of
800 pieces of Rs.20 Renewal reward points
Total benefit of Rs.90
Yes brother season low route medical
insurance of Rs.1 lakh against If you spend more than
2,000 every month on medicines and diseases then
we
have our advance planning for you
whose cost is
Rs.90 plus GST on
which you get medical bills
reimbursement for three years Validity
now you get 50% discount and medicine
A monthly reimbursement of Rs.100 for using
260 Renewal reward points
Total benefit of Rs.1 lakh Cases
number medical insurance Rs.1 lakh If
your monthly expenses are more than this then
you can also take post nice line from us
You can also download our Dekhi IIM IIM app from Google Play
Store and Ayurveda from this episode
I will register you and try the plan
and I will tell you my  Upload the bill of medicines
and every month your expenses will be refunded to your account i.e.
we will also deliver your medicines to you at your home.
I am thinking of subscribing, contact us today
and free your family from the
expenses of medicines and diseases.
If you want to join our company and
take agency or want to apply for a job,
you can also contact us.